<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>digital health on Shahryar Eivazzadeh</title>
    <link>/categories/digital-health/</link>
    <description>Recent content in digital health on Shahryar Eivazzadeh</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 04:44:31 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/categories/digital-health/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Success Factors of Health Information Systems</title>
      <link>/blog_en/2019/2019-12-01-thesis/2019-12-01-doctoral-thesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 04:44:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog_en/2019/2019-12-01-thesis/2019-12-01-doctoral-thesis/</guid>
      <description>Health information systems are our technological response to the growing demand for health care. However, their success in their mission can be challenging due to the complexity of evaluating technological interventions in health care. In the series of studies compiled in this dissertation, we looked at the evaluation of these systems. We focused on the evaluation of factors that lead to success, where success is indicated by user satisfaction and can be induced by both intervention-specific and individual-specific factors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quality Aspects in Health Information Systems, Patterns of Relation</title>
      <link>/media_en/2017/quality_aspects_in_health_information_systems_patterns_of_relation/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/media_en/2017/quality_aspects_in_health_information_systems_patterns_of_relation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Evaluating Health Information Systems Using Ontologies</title>
      <link>/writings_en/2016/evaluating_health_information_systems_using_ontologies/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writings_en/2016/evaluating_health_information_systems_using_ontologies/</guid>
      <description>Evaluating Health Information Systems Using Ontologies Shahryar Eivazzadeh
shahryar.eivazzadeh@bth.se
 Table of Contents Abstract Keywords 1. Introduction and Background 2. Method and Materials 3. Results 3.1. The UVON Method for Unifying the Evaluation Aspects 3.2. Result of the UVON Method Application in the FI-STAR Project   4. Discussion 4.1. Extending the Evaluation Utilizing the Ontology 4.2. Limitations of the UVON Method   5. Conclusion 6. Acknowledgment 7. Conflict of Interests 8.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>From Technology to Health Information Technology</title>
      <link>/writings_en/2015/from_technology_to_health_technology/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/writings_en/2015/from_technology_to_health_technology/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents From Technology to Health Information Technology Health Technology Information Technology Health Information Technology &amp;amp; Systems Simorgh story and the persistence evaluation aspects References      From Technology to Health Information Technology 
  &amp;#8220;Open the pod bay doors, HAL!&amp;#8221;
&amp;#8220;I&amp;#8217;m sorry, Dave.
 I&amp;#8217;m afraid I can&amp;#8217;t do that.&amp;#8221; This scene is a turning point in the 2001: A Space Odyssey movie (1968) and novel when HAL 9000, the main computer of the spaceship and a symbol of top-notch technology, defies Dave Bowman the captain and main character of the story, suggesting that it was the one who plotted the murder of the crew in staged accidents.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
